https://www.littleknits.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to Content
Call - Toll Free: 1.800.877.5852 / Seattle Area: 1.206.535.7720
Welcome to Little Knits!
Compare Products
Little Knits
Menu
Home
NEW PRODUCTSALL ZAUBERBALL SALE!Hot!All HiyaHiya Closeout Sale!Hot!Amano Eco PunaAmano WarmiAnchor Cross Stitch, Embroidery and Needlepoint KitsAraucania HuascoAraucania Nuble PaintsBROWN SHEEP SUPER SALE!Hot!Baby and Kids book/Pattern Sale!Berroco Bento, Ginkgo & Skye Super Sale!Berroco CorsicaBerroco MercadoBerroco MillefioriBerroco Pima 100NewBerroco QuechuaBerroco Sale MixBerroco Tuscan TweedBig Book SaleBlue Sky Fibers Skinny CottonBrown Sheep Legacy Lace NewButton SaleCASCADE SUPER SALE MIX!Hot!Cascade Aegean TweedNewCascade Anchor BayCascade Friday HarborNewCascade ReboundCascade ReverbCascade TangierHot!Cebelia Crochet Cotton Size 10NewClassic Elite EmbraceHot!Coats & Clark ThreadNewDMC Machine Embroidery Thread, Size 50NewDouble Pointed Knitting Needles - 50% Off Closeout Sale!Hot!Downloadable Patterns - No Shipping ChargesDream in Color 18-Ply Merino SuperwashDream in Color Closeout SaleDream in Color Liquidation SaleElla Rae Cozy Alpaca ChunkyElsebeth Lavold Misty WoolElsebeth Lavold Silky Wool & HempathyHot!Embroidery & Cross Stitch SuppliesFeza Gradient KitsFeza RioFeza Sheepy StepsFeza SocktasticFibre-Isle Fine YarnsFleece Artist Sheared AngoraFyberspates Vivacious DKHoliday & New Year Gift KitsJames C Brett Fairy Cakes - BIG 200 Gram CakesHot!James C Brett Super SaleJuniper Moon Farm AineJuniper Moon Farm DromedaryJuniper Moon Farm YearlingJuniper Moon StratusHot!KFI Luxury Collection AdonisKauni & Evilla Closeout Sale!Kraemer Alpaca RovingLace & Luxury Yarn CloseoutsLacis AccessoriesLacis Ebony Crochet HooksLamb's Pride Superwash BulkyLamb's Pride Superwash SportLamb's Pride Superwash Sport & WorstedLana Grossa Lace LuxLang GretaLittle Knits Bergamo & Bergamo LightLittle Knits Serica LuxLittle Knits SockulentLittle Knits Yarns for Hand-DyeingLongwood & Longwood SportLouet Euroflax Sport Weight 100% LinenHot!Louisa Harding AmitolaLouisa Harding Grace Silk & WoolHot!Madeline Tosh Sale Mix!Hot!Maharashtra SilkMalabrigo NubeMineville Single Ply Merino DKHot!Miyuki Delica BeadsNewMiyuki Triangle BeadsMy First RegiaNoro KisoNoro Kureyon AIRNoro TokonatsuNoro TsubameNewOn Linie Punta & SpotPaca PedsPainted Desert & SkyPatternsPure Wool Superwash WorstedQueensland Rustic Merino SportHot!REGIA SOCK YARN SUPER SALE!Hot!Regia Premium BambooHot!Rowan Alpaca Soft DKHot!Rowan Baby Merino Silk DKRowan Felted TweedRowan Kid ClassicRowan Kidsilk HazeRowan Original DenimRowan Selects Softest Merino WoolRowan Super Sale!Hot!Rowan Valley Tweed & Cashmere TweedHot!SIRDAR SUPER SALE MIX!Hot!SUPER SOCK SALESWTC SaphiraSchachenmayr 60-80% Off Liquidation Sale!Hot!Schachenmayr Alpaca Wool Mix NewSchachenmayr Baby WoolSchachenmayr Cotton ClearanceSchachenmayr Fashion Summer OmbreSchachenmayr Kid LightNewSchachenmayr Merino Extrafine 85Schachenmayr Mouline ArtNewScissorsShibui Knits Closeout Sale MixHot!Silky Sheep Hand-DyedSirdar Colourwheel CakesNewSirdar Cotton 4-Ply & Sirdar Cotton DKSirdar Snuggly Rascal DKHot!Stylecraft Super SaleSublime IslaHot!Sublime Yarns Sale MixSupersocke Sweet SocksHot!Swans Island All American SportNewSwans Island All American WorstedNewSwans Island Ecowash Organic Merino Sport & DKHot!Swans Island Natural Colors Collection LaceNewTahki Donegal TweedVenezia Sport and WorstedWYS Wensleydale Gems NewZealana Closeout SaleZitron UnisonoYarnAll About LaceAraucaniaBC GarnBaa Ram EweBartlett YarnsBeads and CrystalsBebe Yarns :)BerrocoBrown Sheep YarnsButtonsCascadeClassic EliteClear Me Away!Debbie BlissDream In ColorElla Rae YarnsElsebeth LavoldEuro & KFI YarnsEvilla YarnsFezaFiber TrendsFibre CompanyFleece ArtistFly DesignsFyberspatesGedifraGeilskHabu TextilesHand MaidenHikooJames C BrettJamieson's of ShetlandJo SharpJojoland YarnsJuniper Moon FarmKatiaKauniKnit One Crochet TooKoiguKraemer YarnsLace is BeautifulLittle Knits YarnsLopiLorna's LacesLouisa HardingMadeline ToshMalabrigo YarnMirasolNamaste Bags & AccessoriesNaviaNoroNovelty & Fantasy Yarn LinesOnLineOoo ShinyOpalQueensland CollectionRegiaRowanSchachenmayr SMCSchaefer YarnShibui KnitsSirdarSkacelSocks, Socks, Socks!Sublime Sweet GeorgiaUniversal YarnsVikingWest Yorkshire SpinnersZealana YarnsNeedles/HooksAddiBrittany Art Deco Birch NeedlesChiaoGoo Needles & HooksDouble Pointed Needles (DPNs)HiyaHiyaHooked On YouKnittingneedlesLacisLykkeNotionsBooks/MagazinesBeroccoClassic EliteCrochet Guild of AmericaDebbie BlissElla RaeElsebeth LavoldFiber Trends PatternsFiddlesticks Knitting PatternsFree PatternsHabu PatternsInterweave MagazinesLouisa HardingMIrasolManos Pattern BooksNashua Pattern BooksNoni PatternsNoro Books & MagazinesOat CoutureRebecca MagazineRowanSchachenmayr/SMCSirdarSnooter-DootsStylecraftVogue KnittingZealanaGift CertificatesGiftCertsOther ProductsBags/CasesHerdyOn Pins and NeedlesSingle Item Free Ship SpecialsTapestry & Cross Stitch NeedlesThreadYarn WashSpinningBrown Sheep SaleDragonFibers Roving - Free Shipping!Frog Tree Meriboo Spinning TopKraemer Mauch Chunky RovingRovingSpinning Wheels
Home
Security & Privacy Policy
PRIVACY & SECURITY POLICY
The security of your personal information is very important to us. In an effort to protect your personal information, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology with 128 bit encryption. If your browser supports SSL (most current browsers do), it will automatically encrypt the information you provide to us on the secure pages on our site, before sending it over the Internet. When visiting a page on our site that includes any of your personal information, the bottom of your browser window will display, an icon of a closed lock or an unbroken key (depending upon your browser). This indicates that you have successfully connected with our secure server.
Little Knits has obtained a digital certificate from RapidSSL (a GeoTrust companny) GeoTrust is a leading provider of Internet trust services. To authenticate the security of your connection before submitting any of your personal information, you can double click on the icon to display our digital certificate.
Some browser versions and some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, we suggest that you contact us by phone or fax your order to us.
COOKIES
When you visit our site, our server will require your browser to place a permanent "cookie" (a very small text file) on your computer. If your browser is configured to accept cookies, it will accept the cookie and place it on your computer's hard drive. We collect this information to analyze where our customers are coming from and how often they visit our site. We also collect certain technical information from your computer, like your IP address and the address of a referring web site, if any. This information will allow us to enhance our site to our customer's preferences. This information is used only for the benefit of Little Knits and you, our customer.
You can visit our site without cookies if you choose to do so. To visit our site without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is set. Check the browsers help menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.
REGRISTRATION
In order to identify who you are, we suggest that you register and log-in tou your account when you visit our site. This allows us to provide you with your Account dashboard which includes order status and other information that is uniquely yours. If you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password.
ACCOUNT ACCESS & MAINTENANCE
You can access all the personally identifiable information that we collect online or mail (3219 California Avenue SW, Seattle, WA 98116 USA), or via e-mail. We use this procedure to safeguard your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows the error. If you place an order with a ship-to address that differs from your bill-to address, we retain this information as well. You can modify or correct this information by following the procedure described above. Such information is used at your request to ship purchased merchandise and may also be used for marketing purposes, but will not be sold to any third parties.
INFORMATION COLLECTED
When you choose to place an order with us, you are invited to log in (optional), so that we can identify who you are. As a newcomer, it will be suggested that you register for future identification. The registration page asks you to enter your name, a user ID, a password, and your e-mail address. You can update this information at any time by clicking on the "Account" link at the top of every page and selecting "update account information."
PLACING AN ORDER
When you decide to place an order, you are asked to complete an order form. The order form requires your name, billing and shipping address, credit card number, expiration date and CID#. You should also include other information fields such as your telephone number, to allow us to contact you regarding your order if necessary. This information is collected to make your shopping experience with us as smooth and pleasant as possible. It is used only for the benefit of Little Knits and you, our customer.
NO INFORMATION SHARING
As described in detail above, any information we gather at this web site is strictly for our use and is not shared with any other entity, public or private, for any reason - period. We will not sell or give away any lists or other data that we may retain and we do not purchase such information from other sources.
INTERNAL ACCESS TO CUSTOMER INFORMATION
Our internal systems and process controls are designed and executed to grant Little Knits employees access to customer information on an as needed basis. These controls require employees to access individually provisioned accounts using secret passwords. Each employee account is defined with restrictions that grant access to only that customer information each individual needs to perform their job responsibilities. The same SSL encryption technology mentioned above is used to protect customer information transmitted through our back office systems.
EXTERNAL LINKS
Our site contains links to manufacturers’ and other related sites for your benefit. Little Knits is not responsible for the privacy practices, security, or content of such web sites. If you click on one of these links, you will be redirected to their web site and, in doing so, you may provide information directly to them. Therefore, you should refer to their privacy policies to understand how they handle your information and what choices you have.
OTHER INFORMATION
Our transaction security, combined with our privacy guarantee, should satisfy your concerns regarding online ordering. Keep in mind however that you have a number of alternate choices available for doing business with Little Knits.
You can order on-line without sending your credit card number over the Internet. Just complete our on-line order form, print, and fax it to us. If you prefer, you can always call 800.877.5852 or 206.535.7720, and place your order by telephone.
If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact admin.site@shop.littleknits.com.
Search TermsPrivacy and Cookie PolicyOrders and ReturnsContact Us
SIGN UP FOR NEWSLETTER
Newsletter
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Address: 3200 Airport Way S.
Bldg 8, Suite 110
Seattle, WA 98134-2141
Retail: We are open and shipping.  Curb-side pick up is available for our local customers.
Company Info
Toll Free: 1.800.877.5852
Local: 1.206.535.7720
customerservice@littleknits.com
Copyright © 2019-2020 Little Knits, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
